PUGG, c++ plug-in framework history file.
http://pugg.sourceforge.net
Tunç Bahçecioğlu

0.5 (nairboon)
	- compiles under gcc 4.2 (darwin)
	- linux & mac support
0.41
	-A memory leak occuring while trying to load dll files not having the registerPlugin function is fixed.
0.4
	-std::wstring file name support
0.3
	-Name convension changes
	-Release pack for the library and related example projects are put together
	-More source code Documentation
0.21
	-Bug Fix related to UNICODE support
0.2 
	-Version control system on plug-in system is removed. Every driver's version is controlled separetely.
	-Server class became template, removing the need to write a server class for every driver and 
		casting the drivers	before usuage.
0.11 
	-Bug fixes 
0.1 
	-Initial release